Srijon Ashraf Zim

Front-End Developer & Graphic Designer

A University going final year student with a strong passion for Frontend Development & Designing, having more than two years of practicing experience in this field. Completed more than five hundred designing projects in freelance career. Seeking opportunities in a dynamic company to expand the expertise and communication skills by working with a good team together.



Work History

2020-06 -Current

Brand Designer

Momo Hut, Darwin

 Momo Hut is an Australian restaurant service provider with more than four outlets there. I've been worked for them for more than 2.5 years as their brand designer. I designed all of visual contents, including main logo of restaurant's, menus, promotional items, and packaging. Still working with them fluently.

2022-01 -Current

Graphic Designer

SS Cafetoria, Khulna

- Developed creative design for print materials, banners and signs for Cafetoria.
- Designed creative digital displays used in online advertising for local businesses which increased their sales by 20%.
- Developed graphics and visual content for social media campaigns.



Education

2020-01 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science & Engineering

Daffodil International University - Birulia, Savar, Dhaka, Bangladesh

CGPA: 3.8 (Current)

• Member of [DIU Computer and Programming Club]



Contact

Address

Dhaka, 1216

Phone

017-222-04560

E-mail

srijonashraf@gmail.com

WWW

srijonashrafbd.xyz

LinkedIn

bd.linkedin.com/in/srijonashraf

Github

github.com/srijonashraf



Skills

Javascript

Very Good

Python

Very Good

C++

Very Good

HTML5

Excellent

2018-01 - H.S.C: Science

2019-01 Khulna Public College - Khulna, Bangladesh

GPA: 5.00

2016-01 - S.S.C: Science

2017-01 Khulna Public College - Khulna

GPA: 4.73



Personal Projects

• Portfolio Website

This website is basically an overview of what I am doing now and my expertise with some visual contents.

Car Games using JS

This is basically a game I made using JavaScript.

Bazar

Frontend Design of an e-commerce website named Bazar.

[Visit my GitHub for the source codes of all projects]

\mathbb{Q}

Certifications

2023-01 AI FOR EVERYONE FROM DEEPLEARNING.AI

2022-06 SEO FOR BEGINNERS FROM GOEDU

2020-04 ICPC DHAKA REGIONAL PRELIMINARY CONTEST



Problem Solving | Technology | Travel

CSS3

Excellent

Bootstrap

Very Good

Git

Very Good

Shell

Good

MySQL

Good

WordPress

Good



Software

Visual Studio Code

Excellent

Git

Excellent

Adobe Photoshop

Excellent

Adobe Illustrator

Very Good